<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home page on It&#39;s pedia - A knowledge base for Everyone</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home page on It&#39;s pedia - A knowledge base for Everyone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</webMaster>
    <copyright>itspedia | 沪ICP备14049619号-3</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;That I exist is a perpetual surprise which is life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;itspedia is &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s pedia&amp;rsquo;, dedicated to knowledge distribution.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about.zh-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about.zh-cn/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;生命对我来说是一个永久的神奇. -泰戈尔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;pedia指百科，itspedia为it&amp;rsquo;s pedia的简写，寓意这就是百科。意在致力于知识传播等相关领域。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radar Trends to Watch: March 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-march-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-march-2025/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropic’s announcement of Claude 3.7 Sonnet notwithstanding, the breakneck pace of major AI announcements seemed to slow down through February. That gave us some time to look at some other topics. Two important posts about programming appeared: Salvatore Sanfilippo’s “We Are Destroying Software” and Rob Pike’s slide deck “On Bloat.” They’re unsurprisingly similar. Neither mentions AI; both address the question of why our hardware is getting faster and faster but our applications aren’t. We’ve also noted the return of Pebble, the first smart watch, and an AI-driven table lamp from Apple Research that looks like it came from Pixar’s logo. Fun, perhaps, but don’t look for it in Apple Stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anthropic has released &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-3-7-sonnet&#34;&gt;Claude 3.7 Sonnet,&lt;/a&gt; the company’s first reasoning model. It’s a “hybrid model”; you can tell it whether you want to enable its reasoning capability. You can also control its thinking “budget” by limiting the number of tokens it generates for the reasoning process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://arena.xlang.ai/&#34;&gt;Computer Agent Arena&lt;/a&gt; is a platform for crowdsourced agent testing. It allows anyone to run an agent using two different AI models, observe what the agent is doing, and rate the results. Results are summarized on a leaderboard; right now, Claude 3.5 Sonnet is at the top.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google is developing a “&lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/google/2025/02/googles-new-ai-generates-hypotheses-for-researchers/&#34;&gt;co-scientist&lt;/a&gt;” that suggests hypotheses for scientists to investigate. The hypotheses are based on the scientist’s goals, ideas, and past research. The company’s looking for researchers to help with testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GitHub has &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/news-insights/product-news/github-copilot-the-agent-awakens/&#34;&gt;upgraded&lt;/a&gt; agent mode for Copilot. It will now iterate on buggy code until it delivers correct results, and can add new subtasks to the original if they’re needed to accomplish the user’s goal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/blog/open-r1&#34;&gt;Open-R1&lt;/a&gt; is a new &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/huggingface/open-r1&#34;&gt;project&lt;/a&gt; that intends to create a fully open reproduction of DeepSeek R1. In addition to code and weights, this project will release all tools and synthetic data used to train the model.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyutai.org/Moshi.pdf&#34;&gt;Moshi&lt;/a&gt; is a new conversational (speech-to-speech) language model that is constantly listening and can handle interjections like “uh huh” without getting confused.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/block/goose&#34;&gt;Codename Goose&lt;/a&gt; is a new open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://block.github.io/goose/&#34;&gt;framework&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a href=&#34;https://block.xyz/inside/block-open-source-introduces-codename-goose&#34;&gt;developing agentic AI&lt;/a&gt; applications. It uses Anthropic’s Model Context Protocol for communicating with systems that have data, and can discover new data sources on the fly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Surrey will be building a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4g9rd4g8w2o&#34;&gt;language model for sign language&lt;/a&gt;. One focus will be translating between spoken language and sign language. The goal is to ensure that the deaf community isn’t left behind by the explosion of AI tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.galileo.ai/&#34;&gt;Galileo&lt;/a&gt; is an agentic toolset for detecting when an AI model is &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/ai-agentic-evaluation-tools-help-devs-fight-hallucinations/&#34;&gt;hallucinating&lt;/a&gt;. It’s particularly important for agentic systems, where an error by one agent leads to misbehavior by others downstream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A group of researchers &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2501.19393&#34;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/simplescaling/s1&#34;&gt;s1&lt;/a&gt;, a 32B reasoning model with near state-of-the-art performance. &lt;a href=&#34;https://timkellogg.me/blog/2025/02/03/s1&#34;&gt;s1 cost only $6 to train&lt;/a&gt;. A very small set of training data (only &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/datasets/simplescaling/s1K&#34;&gt;1,000 reasoning samples&lt;/a&gt;) proved sufficient when the model was forced to take extra time for reasoning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some researchers published &lt;a href=&#34;https://jax-ml.github.io/scaling-book/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Scale Your Model&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a book on how to scale large language models. The book is apparently internal documentation from Google DeepMind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenAI has &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/openai-o3-mini/&#34;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; o3-mini, a small and cost-efficient language model based on its (still unreleased) o3 reasoning model.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anthropic has &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/02/anthropic-dares-you-to-jailbreak-its-new-ai-model/&#34;&gt;deployed&lt;/a&gt; its &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/research/constitutional-classifiers&#34;&gt;Constitutional Classifier&lt;/a&gt; for adversarial testing by the public. The classifier is a system that protects Claude models from jailbreaks and attempts to get Claude to answer questions that aren’t allowed. Early results look very good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/01/31/1110740/how-deepseek-ripped-up-the-ai-playbook-and-why-everyones-going-to-follow-it/&#34;&gt;lesson to learn from DeepSeek R1&lt;/a&gt; is that, given a good foundation model, it’s less difficult than many thought to develop a reasoning model. In the coming months, expect many open alternatives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenAI has introduced &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/introducing-deep-research/&#34;&gt;DeepResearch&lt;/a&gt;, an application based on its o3 model that claims the ability to synthesize large amounts of information and perform multistep research tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sam Altman has acknowledged that OpenAI is on the “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/OpenAI/comments/1ieonxv/comment/maa0dcx/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button&#34;&gt;wrong side of history&lt;/a&gt;” as far as open source AI but also said that addressing the issues was not a high priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alibaba has &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-01-alibaba-advanced-ai-rival-gpt.html&#34;&gt;launched Qwen2.5-Max&lt;/a&gt;, another large language model with performance on the same level as GPT-4 and Claude 3.5 Sonnet. It can be accessed through &lt;a href=&#34;https://chat.qwenlm.ai/&#34;&gt;Qwen Chat&lt;/a&gt; or Alibaba’s cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/transformerlab/transformerlab-app?tab=readme-ov-file&#34;&gt;Transformer Lab&lt;/a&gt; is a tool for experimenting with, training, fine-tuning, and programming LLM models locally. It’s still installing, but it looks like Ollama on steroids.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Om-Alve/smolGPT&#34;&gt;smolGPT&lt;/a&gt; is “a minimal PyTorch implementation for training your own small LLM from scratch.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, Microsoft is complaining that DeepSeek used OpenAI to generate synthetic training data. Those objections didn’t stop it from making &lt;a href=&#34;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/deepseek-r1-is-now-available-on-azure-ai-foundry-and-github/&#34;&gt;DeepSeek available on Azure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two composers &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.google/products/gemini/google-arts-culture-gemini-orchestra/&#34;&gt;collaborated with Google’s Gemini&lt;/a&gt; to create &lt;em&gt;The Twin Paradox&lt;/em&gt;, a work for a classical symphony orchestra.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alibaba has &lt;a href=&#34;https://qwenlm.github.io/blog/qwen2.5-1m/&#34;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; two “checkpoints” to its models, &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/Qwen/Qwen2.5-7B-Instruct-1M&#34;&gt;Qwen2.5-7B-Instruct-1M&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/Qwen/Qwen2.5-14B-Instruct-1M&#34;&gt;Qwen2.5-14B-Instruct-1M&lt;/a&gt;. These models have large 1M-token context windows. Alibaba has also open-sourced its inference framework, which the company claims is three to seven times faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Jiayi-Pan/TinyZero&#34;&gt;TinyZero&lt;/a&gt; reproduces DeepSeek’s R1 Zero, a reasoning model with 3B parameters. Training TinyZero cost under US$30. You could download TinyZero, but you could also make your own for less than the cost of an evening out. Do we need expensive models?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/building-applications-with/9781098176495/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Building Applications with AI Agents&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (early release book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/course/modern-automated-ai/9780135414965/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Modern Automated AI Agents: Building Agentic AI to Perform Complex Tasks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tanagram is &lt;a href=&#34;https://tanagramdev.com/&#34;&gt;promising&lt;/a&gt; a toolset for helping developers understand and work with complex codebases. So far, there are only demos, but it sounds interesting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harper Reed &lt;a href=&#34;https://harper.blog/2025/02/16/my-llm-codegen-workflow-atm/&#34;&gt;describes&lt;/a&gt; his workflow for programming with AI. Developing a workflow is essential to using AI effectively, and Harper has given the most thorough description we’ve seen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Like Linux, &lt;a href=&#34;https://web.dev/blog/ruby-on-rails-on-webassembly&#34;&gt;Ruby on Rails can run in the browser&lt;/a&gt;. This hack uses WebAssembly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://linux.doompdf.dev/linux.pdf&#34;&gt;Linux booting&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/linux/comments/1ifwpl0/i_got_linux_running_in_a_pdf_file_via_a_riscv/&#34;&gt;inside a PDF&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zdnet.com/article/linux-running-in-a-pdf-this-hack-is-as-bizarre-as-it-is-brilliant/&#34;&gt;in Chrome&lt;/a&gt;. PDF implementations support JavaScript; C can be compiled into a subset of JavaScript (asm.js), which means that a RISC-V emulator can be compiled to JavaScript and run in a PDF in the browser, which then runs Linux. An amazing hack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ocr4all.org/&#34;&gt;OCR4all&lt;/a&gt; provides free and open source optical character recognition software. Should you need it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why does software run no faster than it did 20 or 30 years ago, despite much faster computers? Rob Pike has some thoughts on &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/e/2PACX-1vSmIbSwh1_DXKEMU5YKgYpt5_b4yfOfpfEOKS5_cvtLdiHsX6zt-gNeisamRuCtDtCb2SbTafTI8V47/pub?start=false&amp;amp;loop=false&amp;amp;delayms=3000#slide=id.p&#34;&gt;controlling bloat&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As the name implies, &lt;a href=&#34;https://adr.github.io/&#34;&gt;Architectural Decision Records&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/adr&#34;&gt;ADRs&lt;/a&gt;) capture a decision about software architecture and the reason for the decision. All too frequently, this information isn’t captured. It is likely to become more important in the era of AI-assisted software development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/from-c-to-clojure-new-language-promises-best-of-both/&#34;&gt;Jank&lt;/a&gt; is a new general purpose programming language. It’s a dialect of Clojure that incorporates ideas from many other languages, including C++ and Rust, and is built on top of the LLVM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here’s a set of &lt;a href=&#34;https://zknill.io/posts/patterns-for-building-realtime/&#34;&gt;patterns for building real-time&lt;/a&gt; features into applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salvatore “antirez” Sanfilippo’s post, “&lt;a href=&#34;https://antirez.com/news/145&#34;&gt;We Are Destroying Software&lt;/a&gt;,” is a must-read. (It says nothing about AI.) It starts “We are destroying software by no longer taking complexity into account.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bitfield/script&#34;&gt;Script&lt;/a&gt; is a Go library that makes it possible to do shell-like programming in Go. Its biggest contribution is the ability to create pipes; it also has Go functions that are similar to grep, find, head, tail, and other common shell commands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-1&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/videos/software-development-hour/0636920889595/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Development Hour with Sam Newman: Using AI-Assisted Tools to Learn Programming Skills with Simon Willison&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/fundamentals-of-software/9781098175504/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fundamentals of Software Architecture&lt;/em&gt;, 2nd Edition&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Threat actors aligned with Russia are &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/russia-targeting-signal-messenger/&#34;&gt;targeting Signal&lt;/a&gt;, the secure messaging application, with phishing attacks that link users’ accounts to hostile devices. One group sends QR codes that &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.darkreading.com/mobile-security/russian-groups-target-signal-messenger-in-spy-campaign&#34;&gt;look legitimate&lt;/a&gt; but link to a device under their control; another impersonates an application used by Ukraine’s military. The best protection is to &lt;a href=&#34;https://support.signal.org/hc/en-us/articles/360007059212-How-do-I-ensure-Signal-is-up-to-date&#34;&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; to the latest version of Signal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-openssh-flaws-expose-ssh-servers-to-mitm-and-dos-attacks/&#34;&gt;Two new vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; in OpenSSH have been found. One exposes OpenSSH servers to man-in-the-middle attacks; the other can lead to denial-of-service attacks. An update has been released; install it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-02-darkmind-backdoor-leverages-capabilities-llms.html&#34;&gt;DarkMind&lt;/a&gt; is a new attack against reasoning language models. It’s possible to build custom applications (like those in the GPT Store) with “hidden triggers” that modify the reasoning process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new kind of supply chain attack involves obtaining &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2025/02/delivering-malware-through-abandoned-amazon-s3-buckets.html&#34;&gt;abandoned AWS S3&lt;/a&gt; buckets that still hold libraries that are frequently downloaded. The new owner can insert malware into the libraries; the original owner, who abandoned the bucket, can’t patch the corrupted libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/security-is-blocking-ai-adoption-is-byoc-the-answer/&#34;&gt;Security is blocking AI adoption&lt;/a&gt;, particularly in heavily regulated industries. That’s understandable; many of the questions we ask of secure systems can’t be adequately answered for AI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft’s AI Red Team has published &lt;a href=&#34;https://airedteamwhitepapers.blob.core.windows.net/lessonswhitepaper/MS_AIRT_Lessons_eBook.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lessons from Red Teaming 100 Generative AI Products&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. It’s essential reading for anyone interested in building a secure AI system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI is being used to &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/ai-is-spamming-open-source-repos-with-fake-issues/&#34;&gt;submit fake feature requests&lt;/a&gt; and bug reports on open source projects. Many of these may be inadvertent, but regardless of cause, it’s generating problems for software maintainers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux has a number of &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/linux-security-scan-your-servers-for-rootkits-with-ease/&#34;&gt;tools&lt;/a&gt; for detecting rootkits and other malware. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chkrootkit.org/&#34;&gt;Chkrootkit&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rfxn/linux-malware-detect&#34;&gt;LMD&lt;/a&gt; (Linux Malware Detect) are worth your attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/time-bandit-chatgpt-jailbreak-bypasses-safeguards-on-sensitive-topics/&#34;&gt;Time Bandit&lt;/a&gt; is a new jailbreak for the GPT models. The attack causes the model to lose track of past, present, and future. Essentially, you ask GPT how someone in the past would do something that can only be done in the present. It’s unclear whether this attack works on other models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When the price of bitcoin goes up, so does the frequency of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/whats-yours-is-mine-is-your-business-ready-for-cryptojacking-attacks/&#34;&gt;cryptojacking&lt;/a&gt;: hijacking computers to form crypto-mining botnets. It’s claimed that for every dollar of crypto that’s mined, the victim incurs $53 in cloud costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/01/backdoor-infecting-vpns-used-magic-packets-for-stealth-and-security/&#34;&gt;new backdoor to VPNs&lt;/a&gt; has been discovered in the wild, giving attackers access to corporate networks. These backdoors stay dormant until they are triggered by a specially constructed “magic packet,” making them difficult to detect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-2&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/beyond-the-algorithm/9780138268442/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beyond the Algorithm: AI, Security, Privacy, and Ethics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/the-developers-playbook/9781098162191/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Developer’s Playbook for Large Language Model Security&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;web&#34;&gt;Web&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As more people ask AI for product recommendations, marketers will need to optimize product perception by language models. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/02/19/1112076/your-most-important-customer-may-be-ai/&#34;&gt;Does LLMO replace SEO&lt;/a&gt;? Optimizing for an LLM may be the next generation of SEO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dailydot.com/debug/how-to-turn-off-gmail-ai/&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; tells you how to opt out of Gemini features in Gmail and other Google Workspace applications. It’s possible to disable Gemini selectively. Unfortunately, it requires you to have access to the administrator’s console.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/blog/javascript-temporal-is-coming/&#34;&gt;Temporal&lt;/a&gt; object is starting to appear in browsers! Temporal is a replacement for the inadequate Date object. It allows programmers to work effectively with dates and times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://marginalia-search.com/&#34;&gt;Marginalia&lt;/a&gt; is an open source search engine that prioritizes noncommercial resorts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-3&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/the-art-of/9781098102609/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Art of SEO&lt;/em&gt;, 4th Edition&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/beyond-the-algorithm/9780138268442/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beyond the Algorithm: AI, Security, Privacy, and Ethics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quantum-computing&#34;&gt;Quantum Computing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft has created a &lt;a href=&#34;https://scottaaronson.blog/?p=8669&#34;&gt;topological qubits&lt;/a&gt; on a new &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/02/19/1112072/a-new-microsoft-chip-could-lead-to-more-stable-quantum-computers/&#34;&gt;quantum chip&lt;/a&gt;. While its chip currently has only 8 qubits, Microsoft claims it can scale to millions of qubits. Putting this many qubits on a chip would go a long way to solving the problem of moving quantum data between chips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian startup Xanadu has built a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/01/30/1110672/this-quantum-computer-built-on-server-racks-paves-the-way-to-bigger-machines/&#34;&gt;quantum computer using photonics&lt;/a&gt;. It currently has 12 qubits, but the company believes it can scale to larger systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-4&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/course/quantum-computing-fundamentals/9780137872558/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quantum Computing Fundamentals&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;robotics&#34;&gt;Robotics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/02/12/1111409/paleo-robots-extinct-prehistoric-animals/&#34;&gt;Robotic models of extinct animals&lt;/a&gt; are helping paleontologists discover how those animals might have lived: how they walked, swam, and flew in their environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-5&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/intelligent-robots-and/9781394198177/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intelligent Robots and Cobots&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gadgets&#34;&gt;Gadgets&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://repebble.com/&#34;&gt;Pebble returns&lt;/a&gt;? Remember the crowdfunded Pebble smartwatch that was available long before Apple’s Watch? It’s coming back—maybe. And it will be hackable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Something we all need: An engineering team at Apple developed an &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-02-apple-pixar-table-lamp-ai.html&#34;&gt;AI-driven table lamp&lt;/a&gt;. Not available in an Apple Store near you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Writing Well</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/on_writing_well/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:20:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/on_writing_well/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing well is part habit, part knowledge of some fundamental rules, and part giving a damn.
&amp;ndash; Ann Handley, Everybody Writes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing is less about beckoning the muse than hanging in until the typing becomes writing.
&amp;ndash; David Carr, a great journalist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;high-quality-content-is-packed-with-clear-utility-inspiration-and-empathy-for-the-audience&#34;&gt;High-quality content is packed with clear utility, inspiration, and empathy for the audience&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Utility × Inspiration × Empathy = High-Quality Content&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utility means you clearly help people do something that matters to them—you help them shoulder their burdens, you ease their pain, you help them make a decision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspiration means our work is inspired by data (more on this later) or it&amp;rsquo;s creatively inspired (or both). It&amp;rsquo;s fresh, different, well-written, well-produced, nicely designed—and it feels like it could come only from you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathy means you relentlessly focus on your customer. You view the entire world through their eyes—because everything the light touches … !&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release an iOS app with Flutter in 7 steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/flutter-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:10:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/flutter-overview/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;release-an-ios-app-with-flutter-in-7-steps&#34;&gt;Release an iOS app with Flutter in 7 steps&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a Flutter app that you’re ready to release to the iOS App Store?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this video &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@leighajarett221&#34;&gt;‪@leighajarett221‬&lt;/a&gt; shows you how to navigate Apple and Flutter tooling to deploy your app to users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chapters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=0s&#34;&gt;0:00&lt;/a&gt; - Introduction &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=58s&#34;&gt;0:58&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 1: Register your Bundle ID &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=103s&#34;&gt;1:43&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 2: Create a record in App Store Connect &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=127s&#34;&gt;2:07&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 3: Modify your Xcode settings &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=268s&#34;&gt;4:28&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 4: Add your app icon &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=304s&#34;&gt;5:04&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 5: Update your build version &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=361s&#34;&gt;6:01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 6: Create a build archive &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE2bpP56QKc&amp;amp;t=492s&#34;&gt;8:12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step 7: Add to App Store Connect&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;resources&#34;&gt;Resources:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Releasing a Flutter iOS app → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbUxkWnplN3VyZ3l6bnBTMFRSZUhqTUtfQ181QXxBQ3Jtc0tuS19zZThtX2JzeVFDWTZwMU0wd1VpNjF6aXVFQ2p3a3Z3SmI0MG1DcGI4dzlVS2E3MUtraEJ5SERrQUF5blhveTlVQ3JVanNGMjVlclEybnNIMkdPMkRySnJnalc4TFpxNmZDdGtpWGUwX0ctNFE0RQ&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3LjxBCw&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3LjxBCw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple Developer Program → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbWV5OWczT25pU0tMZXZPRTVyM1lkZm9jdG10Z3xBQ3Jtc0tud3pJdDI4NmZDREtnMVBmNXZKSkdNcXNDMUhuLVJUcVp5azc3d0VrNVZ2TnRRbmF5V0VNTEx5U2Y4V3BBN25kelFuTUt0V055MmRQakdkdGxMMWxLQUVzWk12dUdwdmlRbzVJV0hINWdIeWV1eUNoVQ&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3EF1M3w&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3EF1M3w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;App Store Review Guidelines → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbUd3UEU0Tm9pc193d29LdTYtZGVCY2NLZ2ptd3xBQ3Jtc0trRk5GcEtQWGxVVVBjRngwRGVYQWNqaUI4WWQyWEFSa1ctS0JNNWZSd0IwZEhtVDFVV2g3ZmdhNE9hYU9WTFJFOVJySEVkOFdKRmFIS241YUl3NlBxZjZ2RzNEbFNvX2std0JLVjFFQURONFpuTzdkdw&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3SLjxmm&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3SLjxmm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flutter for iOS developers → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqa3BDcXBMaUhOTTdtaUVQYXZoQlNWODZBaFhzUXxBQ3Jtc0trOUVhLWtKM25ycjNZRkpxYlZYTmswcVZJb2pOX1ZMbTNIZGMwZDlNd3AwSWJkQU12OXNaOFMyZVFaZUJ6eElzLXFxNmdDakJ3NXlzSVk5NXUzUjlKdU9obkthYXpDdW04bkRZS0FMYXRDN09IWjdvRQ&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3OFw8Y2&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3OFw8Y2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flutter for SwiftUI Developers → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqa3E0ci1FMFg5YU5VcU9ISXU2ei1XUS1QWHYwUXxBQ3Jtc0ttTW9WbWFWYWoxQkhjdGI2cnJUZWg2YjQyRUswZHN0Zm5DZlA1c3RrbzRIWFJzbkJ3T3F1Z3NDTTNVbW5CbFBMRnFMNkNwWEEzWXdxR3loRV8yRmhQRWNRX2M5X1JPSzB2SEZrWXJNc1lfSUI1S3NXUQ&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3qw26y2&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3qw26y2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wonderous App → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbkFaa0VZLUhxVlJwTUtZUG02TlVqa1h5ZEp4d3xBQ3Jtc0ttd1M1MzdHcFc5aXpMeG9kSnRURlBhSU1yOVRpdDB3SF83dTMxODRhSGVBTEt1bG1NcUcyTmZodGZyczZuY094R1BkazVERWhNd1Bwa19jTkZZbnAyOUZqRERUa25qVlludlA1Y3ZzYlUxbS1fY1E0RQ&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2F3KTcUvD&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/3KTcUvD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further your Flutter skills → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbHJRV1JJeEtHbkgxOVZnUHpTeENpVF9pNHg4UXxBQ3Jtc0ttdU9YalM3dWhzY2psSXljTUp4SkhhRTlzZEJ5NXd1V2E0dU9aNTYyUEt6cmR6d0l5SXFZa0NXSzZObGdhMEJVZ1M1MHNxTHRybTREVFo2T3B5c3FYYnY0WkNxQjBIMHZTRmIzY3dGNzBfRXlPaDUzaw&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2FFurtherFlutter&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/FurtherFlutter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Flutter → &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbnJoQzR3NWY2bGFnZnRfR2w0d2d1Vmx2b0ZOZ3xBQ3Jtc0trdkdKNU9acmJjcnFmeVpGVmF0cXdfMzE4RmdaZXgxcWVfNkhaNTU5NlpQSHRfcmViS3VobkJ0M2NXQXh1WFB6V2UtQ1JaaGdBMEdkOG5kQkJDNUFGeWlBaVpsWXI0a2lGTzV5RWhEYk5fcFR4NHRvbw&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gle%2FFlutterYT&amp;amp;v=iE2bpP56QKc&#34;&gt;https://goo.gle/FlutterYT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Publishers at O’Reilly online learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/top-publishers-at-oreilly-online-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:10:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/top-publishers-at-oreilly-online-learning/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly online learning is one of the largest and most successful online learning platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The publishers at this platform can be found below,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Publisher&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;Number of Media(books/courses/videos)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media, Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;6648&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Packt Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;6491&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;5394&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Apress&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3763&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3440&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Routledge&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1858&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Manning Publications&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1639&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;IBM Redbooks&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1609&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Ascent Audio&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1572&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;CRC Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1461&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Addison-Wesley Professional&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1269&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;For Dummies&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1212&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Business Expert Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1194&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw-Hill&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1068&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Harvard Business Review Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;976&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Peachpit Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;887&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;MIT Sloan Management Review&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;862&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Que&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;808&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Microsoft Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;774&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Berrett-Koehler Publishers&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;760&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Infinite Skills&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;757&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Sams&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;713&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Morgan Kaufmann&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;593&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson India&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;587&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;AMACOM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;581&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Academic Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;553&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Center for Creative Leadership&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;540&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Harvard Business Review&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;507&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;497&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Tantor Media, Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;482&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Sybex&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;481&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Cisco Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;477&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Focal Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;472&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Jossey-Bass&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;465&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Association for Talent Development&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;449&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wrox&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;423&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw Hill-Ascent Audio&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;385&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Adobe Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;382&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;No Starch Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;375&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-ISTE&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;364&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;New Riders&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;363&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Productivity Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;363&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Newnes&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;354&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Syngress&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;349&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Assemble You&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;344&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Rocky Nook&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;333&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Auerbach Publications&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;321&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pragmatic AI Labs&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;310&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Chapman and Hall/CRC&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;306&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;SAS Institute&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;288&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pragmatic Bookshelf&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;275&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;IT Governance Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;262&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Rockport Publishers&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;247&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Make: Community&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;217&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Business&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;217&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Jones &amp;amp; Bartlett Learning&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;197&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-Scrivener&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;193&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Walter Foster&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;172&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson IT Certification&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;166&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Career Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;163&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Woodhead Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;160&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Butterworth-Heinemann&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;158&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;HRD Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;158&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Capstone&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;152&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw Hill Computing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;152&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Visual&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;143&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Chandos Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;132&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Take Control Books&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;123&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;SitePoint&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;121&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Education&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;118&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;GoTop Information, Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;117&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;IBM Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;117&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-Blackwell&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;113&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;HighBridge&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;112&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;FT Publishing International&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;108&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Education India&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;108&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-IEEE Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;105&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter Oldenbourg&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;98&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Education Limited&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;96&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pfeiffer&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;95&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;BCS, The Chartered Institute for IT&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;93&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-Interscience&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;92&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;A K Peters/CRC Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;88&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Recorded Books&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;84&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Simon Sez IT&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;84&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Elsevier&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;79&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;RIBA Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;78&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Bloomberg Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;77&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter Mouton&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;72&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Data Science Salon&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;68&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw-Hill Education TAB&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;67&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Project Management Institute&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;66&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Posts &amp;amp; Telecom Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;63&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Elsevier Science&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;62&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;HarperCollins Publishers&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;62&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Laurence King&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;62&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;China Machine Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;53&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;China Electric Power Press Ltd.&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;49&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;AMA Self-Study&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;46&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;William Andrew&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;42&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wrightbooks&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;41&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-VCH&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;37&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;North Holland&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;36&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Center for Cryptologic History, NSA&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;34&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson International&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;34&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;VMware Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;33&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Bibliomotion&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;31&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Digital Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Life&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;friends of ED&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;29&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Alpha&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;28&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;EC-Council&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;24&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Jenny Stanford Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;24&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;TSO (The Stationery Office)&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Psychology Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;22&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Apple Academic Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Big Nerd Ranch Guides&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;IT Revolution Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Microsoft Corporation&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wrox Blox&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;19&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;DK Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Gulf Professional Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Quarry Books&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Adobe Systems&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;14&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson FT Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;13&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Publishing House of Electronics Industry&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;13&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Skylines Academy, LLC&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;13&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Mercury Learning and Information&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Microsoft, Inc.&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Editorial Almuzara&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Taylor &amp;amp; Francis&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter Open&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Expanding Security&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;FT Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Prentice Hall Business&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-IEEE Computer Society Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;TSO&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Turnbull Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Libros de Cabecera&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Prentice Hall Life&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-VCH Verlag&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Aaron Schlesinger&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;dpunkt&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Kalorama&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pan Stanford Publishing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Pearson Education Canada&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Salesforce.com&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Southeast University Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-AIChE&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;EPFL Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw-Hill Osborne Media&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Oracle Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;PH Professional Business&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Prentice Hall&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;BCS Learning &amp;amp; Development Limited&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Chaz Austin&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter Saur&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;InformIT&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Kohler Music Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;mitp Verlag&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Momentum&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;No Time Labs&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;NSA History Staff&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Sashay Communications&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-ASME Press Series&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Alexandra Levit&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;American Geophysical Union&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;BPS Blackwell&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;De Gruyter Akademie Forschung&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Dorling Kindersley Limited&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Estates Gazette&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Eye on Education&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Fair Winds Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Financial Times/ Prentice Hall&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Informa Law from Routledge&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;JAI Press&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;John Rossman&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;McGraw-Hill/TAB Electronics&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;NBS&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;New Page Books&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media, Inc. Beijing&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;popforms&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Routledge India&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Safari Books Online&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Semantic Studios&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Towards AI&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-IEEE Computer Society Pr&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Wiley-TMS&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Willan&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: right&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;appendix&#34;&gt;Appendix&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;oreilly-media&#34;&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oreilly.com/about/history.html&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/publisher-oreilly-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;O’Relly&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly online learning(Safari Books Online), is one of the largest and most successful learning solutions for technical and business topics available on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media is best known for its color-coded &amp;ldquo;Animal Books&amp;rdquo;.&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/O%27Reilly_animal_book_cover_01.png&#34; alt=&#34;“Animal Books”&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly’s mission is to change the world by sharing the knowledge of innovators. For over 40 years, we’ve inspired companies and individuals to do new things—and do things better—by providing them with the skills and understanding that’s necessary for success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the heart of our business is a unique network of experts and innovators who share their knowledge through us. O’Reilly online learning offers exclusive live training, interactive learning, a certification experience, books, videos, and more, making it easier for our customers to develop the expertise they need to get ahead. And our books have been heralded for decades as the definitive place to learn about the technologies that are shaping the future. Everything we do is to help professionals from a variety of fields learn best practices and discover emerging trends that will shape the future of the tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Begun as a technical writing consulting firm, O’Reilly started publishing books about programming and computer technology in 1984. These books, known for the woodcuts of animals on the cover, became such a pervasive feature of the internet revolution that when, in 2000, the cover of &lt;em&gt;Publisher’s Weekly&lt;/em&gt; declared, “The Internet Was Built with O’Reilly Books,” no one could take exception to the claim. In 1992, O’Reilly published the first popular book about the internet, Ed Krol’s groundbreaking &lt;em&gt;Whole Internet User’s Guide and Catalog&lt;/em&gt;, which helped to popularize the World Wide Web when there were fewer than 200 websites. O’Reilly went on to create the first commercial web portal in 1993, the Global Network Navigator (GNN). GNN was the first site on the World Wide Web to support advertising. GNN was sold to AOL in 1995, one of the first big transactions of the dot-com boom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O’Reilly was long recognized for the conferences and summits it organized. In 1997, the firm launched the Perl Conference to raise the profile of the Perl programming language. Then, in 1998, realizing the need to tell a broader story about the role of free software in the internet economy, O’Reilly invited notable leaders of various free software projects to a meeting. At this gathering, the group formally agreed on a new term to tell their combined story—“open source software”—so the meeting became known as the Open Source Summit. The O’Reilly Open Source Convention, also known as OSCON (and which included the Perl Conference), was one of O’Reilly’s flagship events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2003, after the dot-com bust, O’Reilly’s corporate goal was to reignite enthusiasm in the computer industry. Dale Dougherty, an executive at O’Reilly, coined the phrase “Web 2.0” during a brainstorming session. This then became the name for the influential Web 2.0 Summit run by O’Reilly and TechWeb (formerly CMP Media). Web 2.0 framed what distinguished the companies that survived the dot-com bust from those that died, and identified key drivers of future success, including what&amp;rsquo;s now called “cloud computing,” big data, and new approaches to iterative, data-driven software development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most recent events hosted by O’Reilly included the Strata Data Conference, the AI Conference, the Velocity Conference, the Software Architecture Conference, and the invitation-only Foo Camp (a “Friends of O’Reilly” unconference). In 2016, the company produced 19 conferences across the US, Europe, and Asia. In early 2020, the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) pandemic caused a shutdown of in-person conferences all around the world, and O’Reilly made the difficult decision to close down the conference portion of the business. (The Foo Camp series is expected to continue.) O’Reilly founder Tim O’Reilly continues to be a highly sought-after international speaker, giving keynotes on technology and culture and interviewing some of the world’s top technology leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2004, the company named the “Maker movement” with the launch of &lt;em&gt;Make:&lt;/em&gt; magazine, and in 2005, Maker Faire. As recently as 2019, the flagship Maker Faire in San Mateo, California, drew over 130,000 attendees, and other Maker Faires around the world have collectively drawn millions. In 2012, O’Reilly spun out the &lt;em&gt;Make:&lt;/em&gt; properties into a separate venture-backed company, Maker Media, headed up by former O’Reilly executive and &lt;em&gt;Make:&lt;/em&gt; founder Dale Dougherty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2001, O’Reilly launched Safari Books Online, a subscription-based service providing access to ebooks as a joint venture with the Pearson Technology Group. In 2014, O’Reilly acquired Pearson’s interest in the joint venture, rebranding it O’Reilly online learning, which is now a wholly owned subsidiary of O’Reilly Media, based in Sebastopol, California. The largest and most successful learning solution for technical and business topics available on the internet, O’Reilly online learning has millions of users through B2B, consumer, government, and library channels. Customers include Silicon Valley companies like Google, Amazon, Netflix, and Tesla as well as giants in industrial, banking, and other sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The firm is headquartered in Sebastopol, California, with additional offices in Boston, Massachusetts; Farnham, UK; Tokyo, Japan; and Beijing, China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;packt&#34;&gt;Packt&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.packtpub.com&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/publisher-packt-logo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Packt&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Packt has great content for any technical professional looking to stay relevant and keep their skills up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Packt helps real-world developers put software to work in new ways with over 7,500 practical books and videos covering over 1,000 technologies. With coverage ranging from introductory programming to new and emerging technologies, as well as expert advice from industry-leading figures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;history-1&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2004 in Birmingham, UK, Packt’s mission is to help the world put software to work in new ways, through the delivery of effective learning and information services to IT professionals. Working towards that vision, we have published over 6,500 books and videos so far, providing IT professionals with the actionable knowledge they need to get the job done – whether that’s specific learning on an emerging technology or optimizing key skills in more established tools. As part of our mission, we have also awarded over $1,000,000 through our Open Source Project Royalty scheme, helping numerous projects become household names along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;peason&#34;&gt;Peason&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pearson.com&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/publishser-pearson-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;Peason&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearson Publishing is an established educational publisher, software developer, and provider of training systems. Specialising in mobile learning, it helps raise achievement, improve staff performance and reduce costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;for-dummies&#34;&gt;For Dummies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/publisher-for-dummies-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;For Dummies&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dummies is the world’s bestselling reference brand, with more than 1,600 titles. Dummies aims to help customers solve problems and get up to speed on topics that seem difficult or intimidating. Dummies books cover a rull range of technical and general interest topics from computers, business, investment, marketing, careers, and sales to cooking, health, history, home improvement, language, and travel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dummies has always stood for taking on complex concepts and making them easy to understand. Dummies helps everyone be more knowledgeable and confident in applying what they know. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s to pass that big test, qualify for that big promotion or even master that cooking technique; people who rely on dummies, rely on it to learn the critical skills and relevant information necessary for success.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>数据仓库之架构篇</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/data-warehouse-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/data-warehouse-architecture/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;数据仓库之架构篇&#34;&gt;数据仓库之架构篇&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;数据仓库架构主要有三种类型如下表所示&#34;&gt;数据仓库架构主要有三种类型，如下表所示，&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-list.webp&#34; alt=&#34;三种数据仓库架构&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;各数据仓库架构的主要特点&#34;&gt;各数据仓库架构的主要特点&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-characteristics.webp&#34; alt=&#34;架构特点&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wh-inmon架构&#34;&gt;W.H. Inmon架构&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;wh-inmons-architecture-corporate-information-factory&#34;&gt;W.H. Inmon’s architecture: Corporate Information Factory&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-inmon.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Corporate Information Factory&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ralph-kimball架构&#34;&gt;Ralph Kimball架构&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;ralph-kimballs-architecture-dimensional-data-warehouse&#34;&gt;Ralph Kimball’s architecture: Dimensional Data Warehouse&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-kimball.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Dimensional Data Warehouse&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;独立数据集市架构&#34;&gt;独立数据集市架构&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;stand-alone-data-marts&#34;&gt;Stand-Alone Data Marts&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A stand-alone Data Mart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-a-standalone-data-mart.webp&#34; alt=&#34;A stand-alone data mart&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple Stand-alone Data Marts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dw-architecture-multiple-standalone-data-marts.webp&#34; alt=&#34;Multiple stand-alone data marts&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to create a Hugo site in minutes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hugo-getting-started-quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hugo-getting-started-quick-start/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;quick-start&#34;&gt;Quick start&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn to create a Hugo site in minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial you will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure the site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish the site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;prerequisites&#34;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before you begin this tutorial you must:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/installation/&#34;&gt;Install Hugo&lt;/a&gt; (extended or extended/deploy edition, v0.128.0 or later)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/book/en/v2/Getting-Started-Installing-Git&#34;&gt;Install Git&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You must also be comfortable working from the command line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-a-site&#34;&gt;Create a site&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;commands&#34;&gt;Commands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are a Windows user:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not use the Command Prompt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not use Windows PowerShell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run these commands from &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/install/installing-powershell-on-windows&#34;&gt;PowerShell&lt;/a&gt; or a Linux terminal such as WSL or Git Bash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PowerShell and Windows PowerShell &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/whats-new/differences-from-windows-powershell?view=powershell-7.3&#34;&gt;are different applications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you are a Windows user:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not use the Command Prompt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not use Windows PowerShell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run these commands from &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/install/installing-powershell-on-windows&#34;&gt;PowerShell&lt;/a&gt; or a Linux terminal such as WSL or Git Bash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PowerShell and Windows PowerShell &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/whats-new/differences-from-windows-powershell?view=powershell-7.3&#34;&gt;are different applications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Verify that you have installed Hugo v0.128.0 or later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo version&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run these commands to create a Hugo site with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke&#34;&gt;Ananke&lt;/a&gt; theme. The next section provides an explanation of each command.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new site quickstart
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;cd quickstart
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git init
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git submodule add https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke.git themes/ananke
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;echo &amp;#34;theme = &amp;#39;ananke&amp;#39;&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; hugo.toml
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo server&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View your site at the URL displayed in your terminal. Press &lt;code&gt;Ctrl + C&lt;/code&gt; to stop Hugo’s development server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;explanation-of-commands&#34;&gt;Explanation of commands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/directory-structure/&#34;&gt;directory structure&lt;/a&gt; for your project in the &lt;code&gt;quickstart&lt;/code&gt; directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new site quickstart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Change the current directory to the root of your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;cd quickstart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initialize an empty Git repository in the current directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git init&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clone the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke&#34;&gt;Ananke&lt;/a&gt; theme into the &lt;code&gt;themes&lt;/code&gt; directory, adding it to your project as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/book/en/v2/Git-Tools-Submodules&#34;&gt;Git submodule&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git submodule add https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke.git themes/ananke&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Append a line to the site configuration file, indicating the current theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;echo &amp;#34;theme = &amp;#39;ananke&amp;#39;&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; hugo.toml&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start Hugo’s development server to view the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo server&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Ctrl + C&lt;/code&gt; to stop Hugo’s development server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;add-content&#34;&gt;Add content&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add a new page to your site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new content content/posts/my-first-post.md&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo created the file in the &lt;code&gt;content/posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Open the file with your editor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;title = &amp;#39;My First Post&amp;#39;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;date = 2024-01-14T07:07:07+01:00
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;draft = true
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notice the &lt;code&gt;draft&lt;/code&gt; value in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/front-matter/&#34;&gt;front matter&lt;/a&gt; is &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt;. By default, Hugo does not publish draft content when you build the site. Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/usage/#draft-future-and-expired-content&#34;&gt;draft, future, and expired content&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add some &lt;a href=&#34;https://commonmark.org/help/&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; to the body of the post, but do not change the &lt;code&gt;draft&lt;/code&gt; value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;title = &amp;#39;My First Post&amp;#39;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;date = 2024-01-14T07:07:07+01:00
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;draft = true
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;+++
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;## Introduction
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is **bold** text, and this is *emphasized* text.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Visit the [Hugo](https://gohugo.io) website!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Save the file, then start Hugo’s development server to view the site. You can run either of the following commands to include draft content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo server --buildDrafts
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo server -D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;View your site at the URL displayed in your terminal. Keep the development server running as you continue to add and change content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When satisfied with your new content, set the front matter &lt;code&gt;draft&lt;/code&gt; parameter to &lt;code&gt;false&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo’s rendering engine conforms to the CommonMark &lt;a href=&#34;https://spec.commonmark.org/&#34;&gt;specification&lt;/a&gt; for Markdown. The CommonMark organization provides a useful &lt;a href=&#34;https://spec.commonmark.org/dingus/&#34;&gt;live testing tool&lt;/a&gt; powered by the reference implementation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;configure-the-site&#34;&gt;Configure the site&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With your editor, open the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/configuration/&#34;&gt;site configuration&lt;/a&gt; file (&lt;code&gt;hugo.toml&lt;/code&gt;) in the root of your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;baseURL = &amp;#39;https://example.org/&amp;#39;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;languageCode = &amp;#39;en-us&amp;#39;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;title = &amp;#39;My New Hugo Site&amp;#39;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;theme = &amp;#39;ananke&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make the following changes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set the &lt;code&gt;baseURL&lt;/code&gt; for your production site. This value must begin with the protocol and end with a slash, as shown above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set the &lt;code&gt;languageCode&lt;/code&gt; to your language and region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set the &lt;code&gt;title&lt;/code&gt; for your production site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start Hugo’s development server to see your changes, remembering to include draft content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo server -D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most theme authors provide configuration guidelines and options. Make sure to visit your theme’s repository or documentation site for details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thenewdynamic.com/&#34;&gt;The New Dynamic&lt;/a&gt;, authors of the Ananke theme, provide &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke#readme&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for configuration and usage. They also provide a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo-ananke-theme-demo.netlify.app/&#34;&gt;demonstration site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;publish-the-site&#34;&gt;Publish the site&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this step you will &lt;em&gt;publish&lt;/em&gt; your site, but you will not &lt;em&gt;deploy&lt;/em&gt; it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you &lt;em&gt;publish&lt;/em&gt; your site, Hugo creates the entire static site in the &lt;code&gt;public&lt;/code&gt; directory in the root of your project. This includes the HTML files, and assets such as images, CSS files, and JavaScript files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you publish your site, you typically do &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; want to include &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/usage/#draft-future-and-expired-content&#34;&gt;draft, future, or expired content&lt;/a&gt;. The command is simple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-text&#34; data-lang=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn how to &lt;em&gt;deploy&lt;/em&gt; your site, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/&#34;&gt;hosting and deployment&lt;/a&gt; section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ask-for-help&#34;&gt;Ask for help&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;forum&lt;/a&gt; is an active community of users and developers who answer questions, share knowledge, and provide examples. A quick search of over 20,000 topics will often answer your question. Please be sure to read about &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io/t/requesting-help/9132&#34;&gt;requesting help&lt;/a&gt; before asking your first question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-resources&#34;&gt;Other resources&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For other resources to help you learn Hugo, including books and video tutorials, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/external-learning-resources/&#34;&gt;external learning resources&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>数据仓库之人物篇</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/data-warehouse-hall-of-fame/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/data-warehouse-hall-of-fame/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;数据仓库之人物篇&#34;&gt;数据仓库之人物篇&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;数据仓库领域，在业界有几位公认大牛，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;第一位-william-h-bill-inmon&#34;&gt;第一位 William H. (Bill) Inmon，&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;数据仓库之父，开山鼻祖，著书立说，培训演讲，出版了许多书，详见&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bill_Inmon#Publications&#34;&gt;wiki&lt;/a&gt; 我在这里推荐Building the Data Warehouse这本书，第&lt;strong&gt;四&lt;/strong&gt;版出版于2005。他推崇使用Corporate Information Factory（CIF）的数据建模方法（使用范式模型构建企业数据仓库+各维度模型构建的业务主题数据集市），最近在新的数据仓库架构和实施方面和后起之秀Dan Linstedt合作推动新的搭建数据仓库的方法论 Data Vault&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;第二位-ralph-kimball&#34;&gt;第二位 Ralph Kimball&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;使用维度模型构建数据仓库的开创者（Dimensional Data Warehouse）。他起初在一段不短的时间内就这个构建数据仓库方法论和Inmon的CIF展开激烈论战，最终他的方法论获得业界广泛认可，成为业界构建数据仓库的事实标准。他的书专注于实际实现考虑，以toolkit主题的有三本，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Data Warehouse Toolkit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Data Warehouse ETL Toolkit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Data Warehouse Lifecycle Toolkit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这三本书涵盖架构设计，模型设计，项目管理等多个主题，成为业界从业人员之必读。 这里不得不提&lt;a href=&#34;http://chrisadamson.com/&#34;&gt;Chris Adamson&lt;/a&gt;，业界资深顾问，一个Ralph Kimball方法论的追随者，著有Star Schema The Complete Reference等。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;第三位-dan-linstedt&#34;&gt;第三位 Dan Linstedt&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;创新性地提出使用Data Vault建模方法来设计数据仓库模型，后续推出Data Vault 2.0构建数据仓库方法论，涵盖建模、项目管理、架构和实现等方面，通过成立商业联盟和认证培训等商业手段积极推广。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radar Trends to Watch: February 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-february-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-february-2025/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;developments-in-web-virtual-reality-robotics-and-more&#34;&gt;Developments in Web, Virtual Reality, Robotics, and More&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last month, DeepSeek released its R1 reasoning model (now apparently named DeepThink), with capabilities similar to OpenAI o1. What’s important about DeepSeek isn’t its benchmark results; there are a number of models on the same level as o1. What’s important is that it appears to have been trained with one-tenth the resources of comparable models. Throwing more hardware at a problem is rarely the best way to get good results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthropic has added a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/news/introducing-citations-api&#34;&gt;Citations API&lt;/a&gt; to Claude. Citations builds RAG directly into the model. It allows users to add documents to the context. When generating an answer, Claude includes citations that show exactly which parts of the documents were used in developing the response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenAI has released a research preview of &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/introducing-operator/&#34;&gt;Operator&lt;/a&gt;, its competitor to Anthropic’s Computer Use. Like Computer Use, Operator is a general-purpose agent: It can use a browser to navigate the web, bring back information, and generate new actions to accomplish the user’s request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Berkeley has &lt;a href=&#34;https://novasky-ai.github.io/posts/sky-t1/&#34;&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; Sky-T1-32B-Preview, a small reasoning model that cost under $450 to train. It’s based on Alibaba’s Qwen2.5-32B-Instruct. Sky’s performance is similar to OpenAI o1-preview, and it’s fully open: Training data, weights, code, and infrastructure are all open source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DeepSeek has released its &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-R1&#34;&gt;R1&lt;/a&gt; reasoning model, on which its V3 model was based. R1 has performance equivalent or superior to OpenAI o1 and is significantly less expensive. DeepSeek has also released several &lt;a href=&#34;https://simonwillison.net/2025/Jan/20/deepseek-r1/&#34;&gt;other models derived from R1&lt;/a&gt;, including a number of smaller models based on Llama and Alibaba’s Qwen. All of these models have open code and weights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.latent.space/p/o1-skill-issue&#34;&gt;key to using OpenAI o1&lt;/a&gt; effectively is context, not clever prompting. “Don’t write prompts, write briefs”; give it all the information it needs to solve a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenAI has announced a new technique for training its new reasoning models to be safe. &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/deliberative-alignment/&#34;&gt;Deliberative alignment&lt;/a&gt; trains the models to reason on the safety policies themselves rather than requiring humans to grade model responses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meta has introduced &lt;a href=&#34;https://about.fb.com/news/2023/08/seamlessm4t-ai-translation-model/&#34;&gt;SeamlessM4T&lt;/a&gt;, a multimodal (speech and text) model designed for translation. It can translate speech-to-speech and text-to-speech for nearly 100 input languages and 35 output languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthropic has received &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/news/anthropic-achieves-iso-42001-certification-for-responsible-ai&#34;&gt;ISO 42001 certification&lt;/a&gt;. This certification covers responsible AI and addresses AI design and deployment processes, transparency, testing and monitoring, and oversight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google has released a paper on a new LLM architecture called &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2501.00663v1&#34;&gt;Titans&lt;/a&gt; (a.k.a. Transformers 2.0). The primary advantage of Titans is its ability to scale to very large context windows. In effect, it adds persistent long-term memory to the Transformers model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChatGPT can now &lt;a href=&#34;https://techcrunch.com/2025/01/14/chatgpt-now-lets-you-schedule-reminders-and-recurring-tasks/&#34;&gt;schedule recurring tasks&lt;/a&gt;, making it more like a personal assistant. Tasks can include generating reminders, scheduling, summarizing news, and other chores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AI systems may “think” using &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-01-key-ai-power-inbuilt-special.html&#34;&gt;a variant of Occam’s razor&lt;/a&gt;, which prioritizes simpler solutions to problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mistral has released &lt;a href=&#34;https://mistral.ai/news/codestral-2501/&#34;&gt;Codestral 25.01&lt;/a&gt;, a language model that’s optimized for code generation. It claims proficiency in over 80 programming languages. This new release is faster, supports a larger context window, and gives better benchmark results than similarly sized models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://institutionaldatainitiative.org/&#34;&gt;Institutional Data Initiative&lt;/a&gt; has assembled a large dataset of digitized copyright-free works for training language models. The collection currently has roughly 1 million books; it’s significantly larger than the Books3 dataset that was used to train earlier models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft’s Phi-4 model is now &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/microsoft/phi-4&#34;&gt;available on Hugging Face&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/phi4&#34;&gt;Ollama&lt;/a&gt;. It’s yet another impressive model that can run on a reasonably well-equipped laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-01-source-framework-language-multimodal-ai.html&#34;&gt;4M&lt;/a&gt; is an open source framework for training multimodal AI models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NVIDIA has&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;announced&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/project-digits/&#34;&gt;Project DIGITS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;, a personal supercomputer for running AI models up to 200B parameters locally. The system comes with 128GB of RAM. They will be available in May; the starting price is $3,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;O2 (the company, not the skilled GPT version number) has announced &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.virginmediao2.co.uk/o2-unveils-daisy-the-ai-granny-wasting-scammers-time/&#34;&gt;Daisy&lt;/a&gt;, a language model of its own. It answers fraudulent phone calls in real time, wasting the scammer’s time by impersonating a vulnerable elderly person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ServiceNow/Fast-LLM&#34;&gt;Fast-LLM&lt;/a&gt; is an open source library for training large language models. It can scale to run on anything from a single GPU to large clusters and can train models up to (and exceeding) 70B parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/course/practical-retrieval-augmented/9780135414378/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Practical Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/building-applications-with/9781098176495/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Building Applications with AI Agents&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Puppet joins the group of former open source projects that have an open source fork: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openvoxproject&#34;&gt;OpenVox&lt;/a&gt;. OpenVox promises to be fully Puppet-compatible. The project is looking for sponsors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.wireshark.org/Stratoshark&#34;&gt;Stratoshark&lt;/a&gt; is a new tool for &lt;a href=&#34;https://stratoshark.org/&#34;&gt;analyzing system calls on Linux&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a companion to Wireshark, with a similar user interface that’s designed to help users capture system calls and analyze what they’re doing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Need to write applications for the Cray X-MP in your basement? You’ll need a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kej715/ack&#34;&gt;compiler&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s one that runs on Linux and macOS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sigstore.dev/&#34;&gt;Sigstore&lt;/a&gt; is a project that simplifies digitally signing and managing open source software components. It reduces the burden of establishing provenance for software you’ve developed, along with checking the provenance of software dependencies you use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you generate more code, there will be more code to debug and review. &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/more-ai-more-problems-for-software-developers-in-2025/&#34;&gt;Two-thirds&lt;/a&gt; of developers in groups that use AI are spending more time debugging and resolving security vulnerabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you really need a new terminal emulator? &lt;a href=&#34;https://ghostty.org/&#34;&gt;Ghostty&lt;/a&gt; is getting &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/ghostty-will-get-you-excited-about-using-a-terminal-again/&#34;&gt;rave reviews&lt;/a&gt;. It’s worth trying. &lt;a href=&#34;https://forgejo.org/&#34;&gt;Forgejo&lt;/a&gt; is an open source software forge. It’s a decentralized platform for collaborative software development that includes a self-hosted alternative to GitHub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A startup is building &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenextweb.com/news/scenexus-building-digital-twins-of-cities&#34;&gt;digital twins of cities&lt;/a&gt;. These will be very useful to city planners—and possibly also for emergency response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://leptos.dev/&#34;&gt;Leptos&lt;/a&gt; is a new &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/want-a-web-framework-for-rust-not-javascript-try-leptos/&#34;&gt;web framework for Rust&lt;/a&gt;. Like Sycamore, another Rust web framework, Leptos compiles Rust to WebAssembly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ioccc.org/&#34;&gt;International Obfuscated C Code Contest&lt;/a&gt; is back! (Did you miss it?) For more information, follow @ioccc on Mastodon (fosstodon.org).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nicholas.carlini.com/writing/2025/regex-chess.html&#34;&gt;A chess engine in 84,688 regular expressions&lt;/a&gt;: It’s a regex masterpiece. As the author says, more people should do entirely pointless things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-1&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/how-linux-works/9781098128913/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How Linux Works&lt;/em&gt;, 3rd Edition&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/the-digital-twin/53863MIT63126/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Digital Twin Opportunity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (article)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cybercriminals are distributing malware through &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/cybercriminals-are-not-playing-games-malware-hiding-in-roblox-mods/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roblox&lt;/em&gt; mods&lt;/a&gt;. Discord, Reddit, GitHub, and other communications channels are used to attract users to malware-containing packages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloudflare has successfully mitigated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-mitigated-a-record-breaking-56-tbps-ddos-attack/&#34;&gt;largest DDOS attack ever seen&lt;/a&gt;: 5.6 terabits/second from the Mirai botnet. An important new twist: Attacks are very short-lived, making human response impossible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phishing doesn’t always start with an email. Cybercriminals are placing &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-use-google-search-ads-to-steal-google-ads-accounts/&#34;&gt;Google search advertisements&lt;/a&gt; that direct victims to phishing sites that steal their credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The FBI has &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/01/fbi-forces-chinese-malware-to-delete-itself-from-thousands-of-us-computers/&#34;&gt;forced the PlugX malware to delete itself&lt;/a&gt; from over 4,200 computers. Since roughly 2014, PlugX has been used by the Chinese government to steal data from victims. One suspects that the next version of PlugX won’t have a “self-delete” command.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new ransomware attack called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-abuses-amazon-aws-feature-to-encrypt-s3-buckets/&#34;&gt;Codefinger&lt;/a&gt; encrypts AWS S3 buckets. The attack uses AWS’s server-side encryption (SSE) to generate cryptographic keys that Amazon doesn’t store; they are only known to the attacker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft has &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/01/microsoft-sues-service-for-creating-illicit-content-with-its-ai-platform/&#34;&gt;sued&lt;/a&gt; a group of unnamed (and unknown) developers for compromising legitimate user accounts and using those accounts to generate harmful content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/docker-desktop-blocked-on-macs-due-to-false-malware-alert/&#34;&gt;incorrect certificate&lt;/a&gt; is causing macOS to treat Docker Desktop as malware, preventing it from starting. The problem can be fixed by upgrading to Docker 4.37.2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-web3-attack-exploits-transaction-simulations-to-steal-crypto/&#34;&gt;attack against the cryptocurrency transaction simulation mechanism&lt;/a&gt; tricks victims into approving transactions that strip their wallet of cryptocurrency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2025/01/white-house-unveils-cyber-trust-mark-program-consumer-devices/401991/&#34;&gt;Cyber Trust Mark&lt;/a&gt; is a certification intended to ensure consumers that devices incorporating AI meet certain standards set by the US National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) and the Federal Communications Commission (FCC).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple is discovering that errors aren’t the only problem with consumer-facing AI; the company is also having problems with email and chat summaries that &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crikey.com.au/2025/01/08/apple-new-artificial-intelligence-rewords-scam-messages-look-legitimate/&#34;&gt;make spam and fraud messages look legitimate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2025-01-cybersecurity-products-consumers.html&#34;&gt;Security products based on fear&lt;/a&gt;, along with security sales and marketing practices, are counterproductive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;web&#34;&gt;Web&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regardless of the future of TikTok, &lt;a href=&#34;https://pixelfed.org/&#34;&gt;Pixelfed&lt;/a&gt;—a decentralized application for sharing photos and videos—looks like a good alternative. Like Mastodon, Pixelfed is part of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://fediverse.info/&#34;&gt;fediverse&lt;/a&gt; and is built on the federated ActivityPub protocol.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mrgris.com/projects/merc-extreme/&#34;&gt;Mercator: Extreme&lt;/a&gt; allows you to put the North Pole anywhere you want, and draws the corresponding Mercator map. Aside from being a web masterpiece, it shows just how distorted the Mercator projection is. Sadly, almost all of our maps are still based on it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.marimo.io/guides/publishing/playground/&#34;&gt;Marimo playgrounds&lt;/a&gt; are notebooks (like Jupyter) that run entirely in the browser using WebAssembly. They can easily be created and shared on GitHub or on &lt;a href=&#34;https://marimo.app/&#34;&gt;marimo.app&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Most online organizations have some kind of web-based API access. Now that AI is in the picture, &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/its-time-to-start-preparing-apis-for-the-ai-agent-era/&#34;&gt;APIs must be usable by AI agents&lt;/a&gt;. They need to be properly documented in a machine-readable fashion (e.g., with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.speakeasy.com/openapi#openapi-overview&#34;&gt;OpenAPI&lt;/a&gt;) and as uniform as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/flutter-fork-designed-to-give-developers-release-valve/&#34;&gt;fork of the Flutter project&lt;/a&gt;, called &lt;a href=&#34;https://getflocked.dev/&#34;&gt;Flock&lt;/a&gt;, intends to provide features and bug fixes that users have wanted but that have never made it into the release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://streets.gl/&#34;&gt;Streets&lt;/a&gt; is a 3D version of OpenStreetMap. It takes a long time to load and many of the labels aren’t up-to-date, but it’s impressive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What’s the future of the web? If the web is to be a data source for AI, it will need to get much &lt;a href=&#34;https://tomtunguz.com/back-to-text/&#34;&gt;simpler&lt;/a&gt;, shedding megabytes of JavaScript and CSS in favor of text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Something new in &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2025/01/someone-made-a-captcha-where-you-play-doom-on-nightmare-difficulty/&#34;&gt;CAPTCHAs: Play &lt;em&gt;Doom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and kill at least three monsters. It was built with prompt-driven AI using Vercel’s v0 and runs in the browser with Wasm. Unfortunately, I doubt it will keep bots out for long.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-2&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/principles-of-web/9780137355754/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Principles of Web API Design: Delivering Value with APIs and Microservices&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/mastering-api-architecture/9781492090625/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mastering API Architecture&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;virtual-reality&#34;&gt;Virtual Reality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swave is a startup that is building &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenextweb.com/news/swave-startup-holographic-smart-glasses-funding&#34;&gt;holographic smart glasses&lt;/a&gt; that project true holograms, not just hologram-like effects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-3&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/creating-augmented-and/9781492044185/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Creating Augmented and Virtual Realities&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quantum-computing&#34;&gt;Quantum Computing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new quantum computing technology &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenextweb.com/news/zuriq-quantum-computing-startup-funding&#34;&gt;enables trapped ions to move&lt;/a&gt; around on a quantum computing chip. This allows the developers to build chips that support more qubits efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new kind of quantum refrigerator makes it possible to &lt;a href=&#34;https://phys.org/news/2025-01-cold-quantum-refrigerator-paves-reliable.html&#34;&gt;cool qubits&lt;/a&gt; to 22 millikelvin. At lower temperatures, they will be less vulnerable to errors from noise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-4&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/course/quantum-computing-fundamentals/9780137872558/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Quantum Computing Fundamentals&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;robotics&#34;&gt;Robotics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/01/robotic-hand-helps-pianists-overcome-ceiling-effect/&#34;&gt;robotic hand&lt;/a&gt; has been developed that can train pianists to perform very difficult movements more effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;biology&#34;&gt;Biology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI can be used to &lt;a href=&#34;https://phys.org/news/2025-01-ai-technique-generates-images-thick.html&#34;&gt;sharpen biological images&lt;/a&gt; that have been distorted by light passing through layers of tissue. In the past, this problem has been solved with expensive adaptive optics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radar Trends to Watch: January 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-january-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reader-digest/radar-trends-to-watch-january-2025/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite its 31 days, December is a short month. It’s hard for announcements and happenings other than office parties to get attention. Fighting this trend, OpenAI made a series of announcements: their “12 Days of OpenAI.” Not to be upstaged, Google responded with a flurry of announcements, including their Gemini 2.0 Flash Thinking model. Models appeared that could use streaming audio and video for both input and output. But perhaps the most important announcement was DeepSeek-V3, a very large mixture-of-experts model (671B parameters) that has performance on a par with the other top models—but cost roughly 1/10th as much to train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-V3-Base&#34;&gt;DeepSeek-V3&lt;/a&gt; is another LLM to watch. Its performance is on a par with Llama 3.1, GPT-4o, and Claude Sonnet. While training was not inexpensive, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://buttondown.com/ainews/archive/ainews-deepseek-v3-671b-finegrained-moe-trained/&#34;&gt;cost of training&lt;/a&gt; was estimated to be roughly 10% of the bigger models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not to be outdone by Google, OpenAI &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2024/12/openai-announces-o3-and-o3-mini-its-next-simulated-reasoning-models/&#34;&gt;previewed&lt;/a&gt; its next models: o3 and o3-mini. These are both “reasoning models” that have been trained to solve logical problems. They may be released in late January; OpenAI is looking for &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/early-access-for-safety-testing/&#34;&gt;safety and security researchers&lt;/a&gt; for testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not to be outdone by 12 Days of OpenAI, Google has released a new experimental model that has been trained to solve logical problems: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ai.google.dev/gemini-api/docs/thinking-mode&#34;&gt;Gemini 2.0 Flash Thinking&lt;/a&gt;. Unlike OpenAI’s GPT models that support reasoning, Flash Thinking shows its chain of thought explicitly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jeremy Howard and his team have &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/blog/modernbert&#34;&gt;released ModernBERT&lt;/a&gt;, a major &lt;a href=&#34;https://bdtechtalks.com/2024/12/27/modernbert-llm-encoder/?utm_source=feedly&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;amp;utm_campaign=modernbert-llm-encoder&#34;&gt;upgrade&lt;/a&gt; to the BERT model they released six years ago. It comes in two sizes: 139M and 395M parameters. It’s ideal for retrieval, classification, and entity extraction, and other components of a data pipeline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS’s Bedrock service has the ability to &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/amazons-bedrock-can-now-check-ai-for-hallucinations/&#34;&gt;check the output of other models&lt;/a&gt; for hallucinations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To make sure they aren’t outdone by 12 Days of OpenAI, Google has &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.google/products/android/android-xr/&#34;&gt;announced Android XR&lt;/a&gt;, an operating system for extended reality headsets and glasses. Google doesn’t plan to build their own hardware; they’re partnering with Samsung, Qualcomm, and other manufacturers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also not to be outdone by 12 Days of OpenAI, Anthropic has announced &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/research/clio&#34;&gt;Clio&lt;/a&gt;, a privacy- preserving approach to finding out &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/AnthropicAI/status/1867325190352576780&#34;&gt;how people use their models&lt;/a&gt;. That information will be used to improve Anthropic’s understanding of safety issues and to build more helpful models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not to be outdone by 12 Days of OpenAI, Google has &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.google/technology/google-deepmind/google-gemini-ai-update-december-2024/#ceo-message&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; Gemini 2.0 Flash, a multimodal model that supports streaming for both input and output. The announcement also showcased &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/12/11/1108493/googles-new-project-astra-could-be-generative-ais-killer-app/&#34;&gt;Astra&lt;/a&gt;, an AI agent for smartphones. Neither is generally available yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenAI has released &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/introducing-canvas/&#34;&gt;canvas&lt;/a&gt;, a new feature that combines programming with writing. Changes to the canvas (code or text) immediately become part of the context. Python code is executed in the browser using Pyodide (Wasm), rather than in a container (as with Code Interpreter).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stripe has &lt;a href=&#34;https://stripe.dev/blog/adding-payments-to-your-agentic-workflows&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; an &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/stripe/agent-toolkit&#34;&gt;agent toolkit&lt;/a&gt; that lets you build payments into agentic workflows. Stripe recommends using the toolkit in test mode until the application has been thoroughly validated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon Willison &lt;a href=&#34;https://simonwillison.net/2024/Dec/9/llama-33-70b/#atom-everything&#34;&gt;shows&lt;/a&gt; how to run a GPT-4 class model (Llama 3.3 70B) on a reasonably well-equipped laptop (64GB MacBook Pro M2).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As part of their 12 Days of OpenAI series, OpenAI finally released their video generation model, &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/sora/&#34;&gt;Sora&lt;/a&gt;. It’s free to ChatGPT Plus subscribers, though limited to 50 five-second video clips per month; a ChatGPT Pro account relaxes many of the limitations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researchers have shown that advanced AI models, including Claude 3 Opus and OpenAI o1, are capable of “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apolloresearch.ai/research/scheming-reasoning-evaluations&#34;&gt;scheming&lt;/a&gt;”: working against the interests of their users to achieve their goals. Scheming includes subverting oversight mechanisms, intentionally delivering subpar results, and even taking steps to prevent shutdown or replacement. Hello, HAL?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arcturus-labs.com/blog/2024/11/21/roaming-rag--make-_the-model_-find-the-answers/&#34;&gt;Roaming RAG&lt;/a&gt; is a new technique for retrieval augmented generation that finds relevant content by searching through headings to navigate documents—like a human might. It requires well-structured documents. A surprisingly simple idea, really.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google has announced &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-paligemma-2-powerful-vision-language-models-simple-fine-tuning/&#34;&gt;PaliGemma 2&lt;/a&gt;, a new version of its Gemma models that incorporates vision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GPT-4-o1-preview is no more; the preview is now the real thing, &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/o1/&#34;&gt;OpenAI o1&lt;/a&gt;. In addition to advanced reasoning skills, the production release claims to be faster and to deliver more consistent results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A group of AI agents in &lt;em&gt;Minecraft&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/11/27/1107377/a-minecraft-town-of-ai-characters-made-friends-invented-jobs-and-spread-religion/&#34;&gt;behaved surprisingly like humans&lt;/a&gt;—even developing jobs and religions. Is this a way to model how human groups collaborate?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One thing the AI industry needs desperately (aside from more power) is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/11/26/1107346/the-way-we-measure-progress-in-ai-is-terrible/&#34;&gt;better benchmarks&lt;/a&gt;. Current benchmarks are closed, easily gamed (that’s what AI does), and unreproducible, and they may not test anything meaningful. &lt;a href=&#34;https://betterbench.stanford.edu/&#34;&gt;Better Bench&lt;/a&gt; is a framework for assessing benchmark quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-new-ai-model-aims-to-fix-the-sameness-problem-in-generative-content/&#34;&gt;Palmyra Creative, a new language model from Writer&lt;/a&gt;, promises the ability to develop “style” so that all AI-generated output won’t sound boringly the same.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During training AI picks up biases from human data. When humans interact with the AI, there’s a &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2024-12-bias-ai-amplifies-biases.html&#34;&gt;feedback loop&lt;/a&gt; that amplifies those biases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/hands-on-large-language/9781098150952/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hands-On Large Language Models&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/build-a-large/9781633437166/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Build a Large Language Model (From Scratch)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://btiffin.users.sourceforge.net/up/unicon.html&#34;&gt;Unicon&lt;/a&gt; may never become one of the top 20 (or top 100) programming languages, but it’s a descendant of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www2.cs.arizona.edu/icon/&#34;&gt;Icon&lt;/a&gt;, which was always my favorite language for string processing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What do CAPTCHAs mean &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2024-12-human-bot-longer-ai-agents.html&#34;&gt;when LLM-equipped bots can successfully complete tasks set for humans&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/emilk/egui&#34;&gt;egui&lt;/a&gt;, together with &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/emilk/egui/tree/master/crates/eframe&#34;&gt;eframe&lt;/a&gt;, is a GUI library and framework for Rust. It’s portable and runs natively (on macOS, Windows, Linux, and Android), on the web (using Wasm), and in many game engines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the archivist in us: The &lt;a href=&#34;https://manx-docs.org/about.php&#34;&gt;Manx&lt;/a&gt; project isn’t about an island in the Irish Sea or about cats. It’s a catalog of manuals for old computers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cerbrec.com/&#34;&gt;Cerbrec&lt;/a&gt; is a graphical Python &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/cerbrec-a-framework-for-python-devs-without-ai-experience/&#34;&gt;framework for deep learning&lt;/a&gt;. It’s aimed at Python programmers who don’t have sufficient expertise to build applications with PyTorch or other AI libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GitHub has &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/news-insights/product-news/github-copilot-in-vscode-free/&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; free access to GitHub Copilot for all current and new users. Free access gives you 2,000 code completions and 50 chat messages per month. They’ve also added the ability to use Claude 3.5 Sonnet in addition to GPT-4o.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cognition.ai/&#34;&gt;Devin&lt;/a&gt;, the AI assisted coding tool that claims to support software development from beginning to end, including design and debugging, has reached &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cognition.ai/blog/devin-generally-available&#34;&gt;general availability&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSON5, also known as “&lt;a href=&#34;https://json5.org/&#34;&gt;JSON for humans&lt;/a&gt;,” is a variant of JSON that has been designed for human readability so that it can be written and maintained by hand—for example, in configuration files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AWS has &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/aws-debuts-a-distributed-sql-database-s3-tables-for-iceberg/&#34;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; two significant new services: &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/dsql/&#34;&gt;Aurora DSQL&lt;/a&gt;, which is a distributed SQL database, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/s3/features/tables/&#34;&gt;S3 Tables&lt;/a&gt;, which supports data lakehouses through Apache Iceberg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pingcap/autoflow?tab=readme-ov-file&#34;&gt;Autoflow&lt;/a&gt; is an open source tool for creating a knowledge graph. It’s based on TiDB (a vector database), LlamaIndex, and DSPy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-1&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/the-rust-programming/9781098156817/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Rust Programming Language&lt;/em&gt;, 2nd Edition&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/learning-github-copilot/9781098164645/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learning GitHub Copilot&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://drk1wi.github.io/portspoof/&#34;&gt;Portspoof&lt;/a&gt; is a security tool that causes all 65,535 TCP ports to appear open for valid services. It emulates a valid service on every port. It makes it difficult for an attacker to determine which ports are actually open without probing each port.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://letsencrypt.org/&#34;&gt;Let’s Encrypt&lt;/a&gt;, which issues the certificates that websites (and other applications) use to prove their identities, has announced &lt;a href=&#34;https://letsencrypt.org/2024/12/11/eoy-letter-2024/&#34;&gt;short-lived certificates&lt;/a&gt; that expire after six days. Short-lived certificates increase security by minimizing exposure if a private key is compromised.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Because of the continued presence of attackers within telecommunications networks, the US FBI and CISA have &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/white-house-salt-typhoon-hacked-telcos-in-dozens-of-countries/&#34;&gt;recommended&lt;/a&gt; the use of encrypted communications protocols. (Though they still want backdoors into encryption systems, which would make them vulnerable to attack.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/novel-phising-campaign-uses-corrupted-word-documents-to-evade-security/&#34;&gt;new phishing attack&lt;/a&gt; uses corrupted Word documents to bypass security checks. While the documents are corrupt, Word is able to recover them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.knostic.ai/blog/introducing-a-new-class-of-ai-attacks-flowbreaking&#34;&gt;LLM Flowbreaking&lt;/a&gt; is a new class of attack against language models that prevent guardrails from stopping objectionable output from reaching the user. These attacks take advantage of race conditions in the application’s interaction with users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/security/2024/11/found-in-the-wild-the-worlds-first-unkillable-uefi-bootkit-for-linux/&#34;&gt;Bootkitty&lt;/a&gt; is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/researchers-discover-bootkitty-first-uefi-bootkit-malware-for-linux/&#34;&gt;UEFI rootkit&lt;/a&gt; that targets secure boot on Ubuntu systems. It appears to have been developed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bootkitty-uefi-malware-exploits-logofail-to-infect-linux-systems/&#34;&gt;cybersecurity students in Korea&lt;/a&gt;, then leaked (possibly accidentally). It hasn’t yet been found in the wild, but when it is, it will be a dangerous threat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DEF CON has started a project to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theregister.com/2024/11/24/water_defcon_hacker/&#34;&gt;improve cybersecurity for water infrastructure&lt;/a&gt; in the US. They’re starting with six water companies serving rural communities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;more-from-the-learning-platform-2&#34;&gt;More from the Learning Platform&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/course/comptia-security-sy0-701/9780138251062/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;CompTIA Security+ SY0-701&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (video)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/fighting-phishing/9781394249206/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fighting Phishing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (book)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quantum-computing&#34;&gt;Quantum Computing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google has &lt;a href=&#34;https://arstechnica.com/science/2024/12/google-gets-an-error-corrected-quantum-bit-to-be-stable-for-an-hour/&#34;&gt;built&lt;/a&gt; a &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.google/technology/research/google-willow-quantum-chip/&#34;&gt;quantum computing chip&lt;/a&gt; in which an &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2408.13687v1&#34;&gt;error-corrected logical qubit&lt;/a&gt; can remain stable for an hour. It passes the “below threshold”: the error rate decreases as physical qubits are added for error correction. The chip was built in Google’s new fabrication facility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;web&#34;&gt;Web&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google is adding “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-chromes-ai-feature-lets-you-quickly-check-website-trustworthiness/&#34;&gt;store reviews&lt;/a&gt;” to Chrome. Reviews are AI-generated summaries of reports from well-known sources that report scams and other issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here’s a how-to on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.phpied.com/ai-streaming-text-ui-how-to/&#34;&gt;building streaming text user interfaces&lt;/a&gt; on the web. Streaming text is almost a necessity for building AI-driven chatbots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;biology&#34;&gt;Biology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes, we can have virtual taste. A research group has developed a &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2024-11-lollipop-interface-simulating-virtual-environments.html&#34;&gt;lollipop interface&lt;/a&gt; so that people can experience taste in virtual worlds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tutorials: toc</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/2-toc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/2-toc/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;header&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-1&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-2&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;subheader&#34;&gt;SubHeader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;this-is-very-long-subheader--this-is-very-long-subheader--this-is-very-long-subheader-this-is-very-long-subheader--this-is-very-long-subheader-this-is-very-long-subheader&#34;&gt;This is very long SubHeader,  This is very long SubHeader,  This is very long SubHeader, This is very long SubHeader,  This is very long SubHeader, This is very long SubHeader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;subheader-1&#34;&gt;SubHeader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-3&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-4&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-5&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-6&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;subheader-2&#34;&gt;SubHeader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;subheader-3&#34;&gt;SubHeader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;h4&#34;&gt;H4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;h4-1&#34;&gt;H4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;h5&#34;&gt;H5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;h6&#34;&gt;H6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-7&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-8&#34;&gt;Header&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials: Math</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/5-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/5-math/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.intmath.com/cg5/katex-mathjax-comparison.php&#34;&gt;KaTeX and MathJax Comparison Demo, currently processed as KaTeX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;repeating-fractions&#34;&gt;Repeating fractions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\frac{1}{\Bigl(\sqrt{\phi \sqrt{5}}-\phi\Bigr) e^{\frac25 \pi}} \equiv 1+\frac{e^{-2\pi}} {1+\frac{e^{-4\pi}} {1+\frac{e^{-6\pi}} {1+\frac{e^{-8\pi}} {1+\cdots} } } }
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;summation-notation&#34;&gt;Summation notation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\left( \sum_{k=1}^n a_k b_k \right)^2 \leq \left( \sum_{k=1}^n a_k^2 \right) \left( \sum_{k=1}^n b_k^2 \right)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sum-of-a-series&#34;&gt;Sum of a Series&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I broke up the next two examples into separate lines so it behaves better on a mobile phone. That&amp;rsquo;s why they include \displaystyle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle\sum_{i=1}^{k+1}i
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle= \left(\sum_{i=1}^{k}i\right) +(k+1)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle= \frac{k(k+1)}{2}+k+1
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle= \frac{k(k+1)+2(k+1)}{2}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle= \frac{(k+1)(k+2)}{2}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle= \frac{(k+1)((k+1)+1)}{2}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;product-notation&#34;&gt;Product notation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\displaystyle 1 + \frac{q^2}{(1-q)}+\frac{q^6}{(1-q)(1-q^2)}+\cdots = \displaystyle \prod_{j=0}^{\infty}\frac{1}{(1-q^{5j+2})(1-q^{5j+3})}, \displaystyle\text{ for }\lvert q\rvert &amp;lt; 1.
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;inline-math&#34;&gt;Inline math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is some in-line math: $$ k_{n+1} = n^2 + k_n^2 - k_{n-1} $$ , followed by some more text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;greek-letters&#34;&gt;Greek Letters&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\Gamma\ \Delta\ \Theta\ \Lambda\ \Xi\ \Pi\ \Sigma\ \Upsilon\ \Phi\ \Psi\ \Omega
\alpha\ \beta\ \gamma\ \delta\ \epsilon\ \zeta\ \eta\ \theta\ \iota\ \kappa\ \lambda\ \mu\ \nu\ \xi \ \omicron\ \pi\ \rho\ \sigma\ \tau\ \upsilon\ \phi\ \chi\ \psi\ \omega\ \varepsilon\ \vartheta\ \varpi\ \varrho\ \varsigma\ \varphi
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;arrows&#34;&gt;Arrows&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\gets\ \to\ \leftarrow\ \rightarrow\ \uparrow\ \Uparrow\ \downarrow\ \Downarrow\ \updownarrow\ \Updownarrow
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\Leftarrow\ \Rightarrow\ \leftrightarrow\ \Leftrightarrow\ \mapsto\ \hookleftarrow
\leftharpoonup\ \leftharpoondown\ \rightleftharpoons\ \longleftarrow\ \Longleftarrow\ \longrightarrow
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\Longrightarrow\ \longleftrightarrow\ \Longleftrightarrow\ \longmapsto\ \hookrightarrow\ \rightharpoonup
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\rightharpoondown\ \leadsto\ \nearrow\ \searrow\ \swarrow\ \nwarrow
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;symbols&#34;&gt;Symbols&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\surd\ \barwedge\ \veebar\ \odot\ \oplus\ \otimes\ \oslash\ \circledcirc\ \boxdot\ \bigtriangleup
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\bigtriangledown\ \dagger\ \diamond\ \star\ \triangleleft\ \triangleright\ \angle\ \infty\ \prime\ \triangle
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;calculus&#34;&gt;Calculus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\int u \frac{dv}{dx},dx=uv-\int \frac{du}{dx}v,dx
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f(x) = \int_{-\infty}^\infty \hat f(\xi),e^{2 \pi i \xi x}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\oint \vec{F} \cdot d\vec{s}=0
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lorenz-equations&#34;&gt;Lorenz Equations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\begin{aligned} \dot{x} &amp;amp; = \sigma(y-x) \ \dot{y} &amp;amp; = \rho x - y - xz \ \dot{z} &amp;amp; = -\beta z + xy \end{aligned}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cross-product&#34;&gt;Cross Product&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This works in KaTeX, but the separation of fractions in this environment is not so good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\mathbf{V}_1 \times \mathbf{V}_2 = \begin{vmatrix} \mathbf{i} &amp;amp; \mathbf{j} &amp;amp; \mathbf{k} \ \frac{\partial X}{\partial u} &amp;amp; \frac{\partial Y}{\partial u} &amp;amp; 0 \ \frac{\partial X}{\partial v} &amp;amp; \frac{\partial Y}{\partial v} &amp;amp; 0 \end{vmatrix}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a workaround: make the fractions smaller with an extra class that targets the spans with &amp;ldquo;mfrac&amp;rdquo; class (makes no difference in the MathJax case):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\mathbf{V}_1 \times \mathbf{V}_2 = \begin{vmatrix} \mathbf{i} &amp;amp; \mathbf{j} &amp;amp; \mathbf{k} \ \frac{\partial X}{\partial u} &amp;amp; \frac{\partial Y}{\partial u} &amp;amp; 0 \ \frac{\partial X}{\partial v} &amp;amp; \frac{\partial Y}{\partial v} &amp;amp; 0 \end{vmatrix}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;accents&#34;&gt;Accents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\hat{x}\ \vec{x}\ \ddot{x}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;stretchy-brackets&#34;&gt;Stretchy brackets&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\left(\frac{x^2}{y^3}\right)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;evaluation-at-limits&#34;&gt;Evaluation at limits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\left.\frac{x^3}{3}\right|_0^1
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;case-definitions&#34;&gt;Case definitions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f(n) = \begin{cases} \frac{n}{2}, &amp;amp; \text{if } n\text{ is even} \ 3n+1, &amp;amp; \text{if } n\text{ is odd} \end{cases}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;maxwells-equations&#34;&gt;Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s Equations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\begin{aligned} \nabla \times \vec{\mathbf{B}} -, \frac1c, \frac{\partial\vec{\mathbf{E}}}{\partial t} &amp;amp; = \frac{4\pi}{c}\vec{\mathbf{j}} \ \nabla \cdot \vec{\mathbf{E}} &amp;amp; = 4 \pi \rho \ \nabla \times \vec{\mathbf{E}}, +, \frac1c, \frac{\partial\vec{\mathbf{B}}}{\partial t} &amp;amp; = \vec{\mathbf{0}} \ \nabla \cdot \vec{\mathbf{B}} &amp;amp; = 0 \end{aligned}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These equations are quite cramped. We can add vertical spacing using (for example) [1em] after each line break (\). as you can see here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\begin{aligned} \nabla \times \vec{\mathbf{B}} -, \frac1c, \frac{\partial\vec{\mathbf{E}}}{\partial t} &amp;amp; = \frac{4\pi}{c}\vec{\mathbf{j}} \[1em] \nabla \cdot \vec{\mathbf{E}} &amp;amp; = 4 \pi \rho \[0.5em] \nabla \times \vec{\mathbf{E}}, +, \frac1c, \frac{\partial\vec{\mathbf{B}}}{\partial t} &amp;amp; = \vec{\mathbf{0}} \[1em] \nabla \cdot \vec{\mathbf{B}} &amp;amp; = 0 \end{aligned}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;statistics&#34;&gt;Statistics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definition of combination:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\frac{n!}{k!(n-k)!} = {^n}C_k
{n \choose k}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fractions-on-fractions&#34;&gt;Fractions on fractions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\frac{\frac{1}{x}+\frac{1}{y}}{y-z}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;n-th-root&#34;&gt;n-th root&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\sqrt[n]{1+x+x^2+x^3+\ldots}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;matrices&#34;&gt;Matrices&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\begin{pmatrix} a_{11} &amp;amp; a_{12} &amp;amp; a_{13}\ a_{21} &amp;amp; a_{22} &amp;amp; a_{23}\ a_{31} &amp;amp; a_{32} &amp;amp; a_{33} \end{pmatrix}
\begin{bmatrix} 0 &amp;amp; \cdots &amp;amp; 0 \ \vdots &amp;amp; \ddots &amp;amp; \vdots \ 0 &amp;amp; \cdots &amp;amp; 0 \end{bmatrix}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;punctuation&#34;&gt;Punctuation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f(x) = \sqrt{1+x} \quad (x \ge -1)
f(x) \sim x^2 \quad (x\to\infty)
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now with punctuation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f(x) = \sqrt{1+x}, \quad x \ge -1
f(x) \sim x^2, \quad x\to\infty
$$&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials: more Shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/7-shortcodes-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/7-shortcodes-preview/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-a-shortcode-is&#34;&gt;What a Shortcode is&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo loves Markdown because of its simple content format, but there are times when Markdown falls short. Often, content authors are forced to add raw HTML (e.g., video &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;iframes&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;) to Markdown content. We think this contradicts the beautiful simplicity of Markdown&amp;rsquo;s syntax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo created &lt;strong&gt;shortcodes&lt;/strong&gt; to circumvent these limitations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A shortcode is a simple snippet inside a content file that Hugo will render using a predefined template. Note that shortcodes will not work in template files. If you need the type of drop-in functionality that shortcodes provide but in a template, you most likely want a [partial template][partials] instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to cleaner Markdown, shortcodes can be updated any time to reflect new classes, techniques, or standards. At the point of site generation, Hugo shortcodes will easily merge in your changes. You avoid a possibly complicated search and replace operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details: &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/&#34;&gt;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blockquotes&#34;&gt;blockquotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Normal quote:











  





  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a simple quote.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quote with author:











  
  
  
  





  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a quote with only an Author named Author2.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Author2&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quote with author and source:











  
  
  
  





  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a quote from Author3 and source &amp;ldquo;source.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Author3&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      &lt;cite&gt;Source&lt;/cite&gt;
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quote with author and link:











  
  
  
  





      
      
      
    
     
      
    
    

    
    
  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a quote from Author4 and links to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Author4&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        &lt;cite&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34; title=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;google.com&lt;/a&gt; 
        &lt;/cite&gt;
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quote with author, link and title:











  
  
  
  





  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a quote from Author5 and links to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com&lt;/a&gt; with title &amp;ldquo;Google.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Author5&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        &lt;cite&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34; title=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; 
        &lt;/cite&gt;
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quote with author and a link longer than 32 characters, string is first cut at 32 characters then everything after the last forward slash is removed











  
  
  
  





      
      
      
    
     
      
    
    

    
    
         
         
         

         
        
        
        
        
      
      
    
  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a quote from Author5 and links to &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/CryptoGangsta/status/716427930126196737&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/CryptoGangsta/status/716427930126196737&lt;/a&gt; which is longer than 32 characters.
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;And this is a new line in the quote with the HTML br tag.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;Author6&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        &lt;cite&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/CryptoGangsta/status/716427930126196737&#34; title=&#34;https://twitter.com/CryptoGangsta/status/716427930126196737&#34;&gt;twitter.com/CryptoGangsta/...&lt;/a&gt; 
        &lt;/cite&gt;
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test from the Octopress blockquote page at: &lt;a href=&#34;http://octopress.org/docs/plugins/blockquote/&#34;&gt;http://octopress.org/docs/plugins/blockquote/&lt;/a&gt;











  
  
  
  





      
      
      
    
     
      
    
    

    
    
         
         
         

         
        
        
        
        
        
        
      
      
    
  


&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Over the past 24 hours I&amp;rsquo;ve been reflecting on my life &amp;amp; I&amp;rsquo;ve realized only one thing. I need a medieval battle axe.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;footer&gt;
    &lt;strong&gt;@allanbranch&lt;/strong&gt;
    
      
        &lt;cite&gt;
          &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/allanbranch/status/90766146063712256&#34; title=&#34;https://twitter.com/allanbranch/status/90766146063712256&#34;&gt;twitter.com/allanbranch/status/...&lt;/a&gt; 
        &lt;/cite&gt;
      
    
  &lt;/footer&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;music&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gist&#34;&gt;gist&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can embed the gist in our content via username and gist ID pulled from the URL:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gist spf13 7896402 &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/spf13/7896402.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;expand&#34;&gt;expand&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Expand shortcode displays an expandable/collapsible section of text on your page. Here is an example&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary style=&#34;background-color:#f5f5f5;border:1px solid #ccc;padding:5px;&#34;&gt;
    Is this learn theme rocks ?
    
  &lt;/summary&gt;
  Yes !.
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;usage&#34;&gt;Usage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this shortcode takes exactly one optional parameter to define the text that appears next to the expand/collapse icon. (default is “Click to expand”)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; expand &amp;#34;Is this learn theme rocks ?&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}
Yes !.
{{&amp;lt; /expand &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;youtube&#34;&gt;youtube&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w7Ft2ymGmfc?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;vimeo&#34;&gt;vimeo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/146022717&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;vimeo video&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;youku&#34;&gt;youku&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.youku.com/embed/XMzQ0ODUxMjM2NA?autoplay=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34; title=&#34;YouKu Video&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tutorials: Image</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/1-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/1-image/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks for &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/liwenyip/hugo-easy-gallery&#34;&gt;liwenyip/hugo-easy-gallery&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/xianmin/hugo-theme-jane/pull/48&#34;&gt;Zebradil · Pull Request #48&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we could use &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcode in hugo-theme-jane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;normal-image&#34;&gt;Normal Image&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an image in &lt;code&gt;static/image&lt;/code&gt; folder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;![&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;This is an image in `static/image` folder.&lt;/span&gt;](&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;/image/example.jpg&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-figure--shortcode&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcode&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;figure-image-with-title&#34;&gt;figure image with title&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;#34;/image/example.jpg&amp;#34; title=&amp;#34;figure image with title&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;figure-image-with-caption&#34;&gt;figure image with caption&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;#34;/image/example.jpg&amp;#34; caption=&amp;#34;figure image with caption figure image with caption figure image with caption figure image with caption figure image with caption&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;more--figure--shortcode-usage&#34;&gt;more &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcode usage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specifying your image files:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;quot;thumb.jpg&amp;quot; link=&amp;quot;image.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; will use &lt;code&gt;thumb.jpg&lt;/code&gt; for thumbnail and &lt;code&gt;image.jpg&lt;/code&gt; for lightbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;quot;image.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure link=&amp;quot;image.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; will use &lt;code&gt;image.jpg&lt;/code&gt; for both thumbnail and lightbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure link=&amp;quot;image.jpg&amp;quot; thumb=&amp;quot;-small&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; will use &lt;code&gt;image-small.jpg&lt;/code&gt; for thumbnail and &lt;code&gt;image.jpg&lt;/code&gt; for lightbox&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/extras/shortcodes&#34;&gt;features/parameters&lt;/a&gt; of Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in &lt;code&gt;figure&lt;/code&gt; shortcode work as normal, i.e. src, link, title, caption, class, attr (attribution), attrlink, alt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;size&lt;/code&gt; (e.g. &lt;code&gt;size=&amp;quot;1024x768&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;) pre-defines the image size for PhotoSwipe. Use this option if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to pre-load the linked image to determine its size.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt; allows you to set any custom classes you want on the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;figure&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optional parameters for standalone &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcodes only (i.e. don&amp;rsquo;t use on &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; figure &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; inside &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; - strange things may happen if you do):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;caption-position&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;caption-effect&lt;/code&gt; work the same as for the &lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcode (see below).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;width&lt;/code&gt; defines the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.w3schools.com/cssref/pr_dim_max-width.asp&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;max-width&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the image displayed on the page. If using a thumbnail for a standalone figure, set this equal to your thumbnail&amp;rsquo;s native width to make the captions behave properly (or feel free to come up with a better solution and submit a pull request :-)). Also use this option if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a thumbnail and you don&amp;rsquo;t want the hi-res image to take up the entire width of the screen/container.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class=&amp;quot;no-photoswipe&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt; prevents a &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;figure&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; from being loaded into PhotoSwipe. If you click on the figure you&amp;rsquo;ll instead a good ol&amp;rsquo; fashioned hyperlink to a bigger image (or - if you haven&amp;rsquo;t specified a bigger image - the same one).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-gallery--shortcode&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt; shortcode&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;simple-gallery&#34;&gt;simple gallery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To specify a directory of image files:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery dir=&amp;#34;/img/your-directory-of-images/&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The images are automatically captioned with the file name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;[image].jpg&lt;/code&gt; is used for the hi-res image, and &lt;code&gt;[image]-thumb.jpg&lt;/code&gt; is used for the thumbnails.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If &lt;code&gt;[image]-thumb.jpg&lt;/code&gt; doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, then &lt;code&gt;[image].jpg&lt;/code&gt; will be used for both hi-res and thumbnail images.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The default thumbnail suffix is &lt;code&gt;-thumb&lt;/code&gt;, but you can specify a different one e.g. &lt;code&gt;thumb=&amp;quot;-small&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;thumb=&amp;quot;_150x150&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;to-specify-individual-image-files&#34;&gt;To specify individual image files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{&amp;lt; gallery &amp;gt;}}
  {{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;#34;image1.jpg&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}
  {{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;#34;image2.jpg&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}
  {{&amp;lt; figure src=&amp;#34;image3.jpg&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; /gallery &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional parameters:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;caption-position&lt;/code&gt; - determines the captions&amp;rsquo; position over the image. Options:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;bottom&lt;/code&gt; (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;center&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;none&lt;/code&gt; hides captions on the page (they will only show in PhotoSwipe)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;caption-effect&lt;/code&gt; - determines if/how captions appear upon hover. Options:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;slide&lt;/code&gt; (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;fade&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;none&lt;/code&gt; (captions always visible)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;hover-effect&lt;/code&gt; - determines if/how images change upon hover. Options:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;zoom&lt;/code&gt; (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;grow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;shrink&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;slideup&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;slidedown&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;none&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;hover-transition&lt;/code&gt; - determines if/how images change upon hover. Options:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;not set - smooth transition (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;none&lt;/code&gt; - hard transition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tutorials: Shortcodes Notice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/6-shortcode-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/6-shortcode-notice/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;normal-use&#34;&gt;normal use&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Note&lt;/code&gt; example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{% notice note %}}
A notice disclaimer
{{% /notice %}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Result:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could &lt;strong&gt;custom title&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{% notice note 笔记 %}}
A notice disclaimer
{{% /notice %}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip&#34;&gt;tip&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{% notice tip %}}
A tip disclaimer
{{% /tip %}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;info&#34;&gt;info&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{% notice info %}}
A info disclaimer
{{% /notice %}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;warning&#34;&gt;warning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{% notice warning %}}
A warning disclaimer
{{% /notice %}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials: Footnote</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/4-footnote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/4-footnote/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo-theme-jane optimized for footnote. When you mouse hover the footnote&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; , footnote content will be displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnote-1&#34;&gt;Footnote-1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can create footnotes like this[^footnote].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[^footnote]: Here is the &lt;span style=&#34;font-style:italic&#34;&gt;*text*&lt;/span&gt; of the &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold&#34;&gt;**footnote**&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will produce:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create footnotes like this&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mouse on the ‘footnote’ superscript to see content of the footnote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnote-2&#34;&gt;Footnote-2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can create footnotes like this[^footnote2].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[^footnote2]: Here is the &lt;span style=&#34;font-style:italic&#34;&gt;*text*&lt;/span&gt; of the &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold&#34;&gt;**footnote**&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will produce:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create footnotes like this&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mouse on the ‘footnote’ superscript to see content of the footnote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnote-3&#34;&gt;Footnote-3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can create footnotes like this[^footnote].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[^footnote]: Here is the &lt;span style=&#34;font-style:italic&#34;&gt;*text*&lt;/span&gt; of the &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold&#34;&gt;**footnote**&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will produce:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create footnotes like this&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:4&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mouse on the ‘footnote’ superscript to see content of the footnote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnote-4&#34;&gt;Footnote-4&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can create footnotes like this[^footnote].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[^footnote]: Here is the &lt;span style=&#34;font-style:italic&#34;&gt;*text*&lt;/span&gt; of the &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold&#34;&gt;**footnote**&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will produce:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create footnotes like this&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:5&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mouse on the ‘footnote’ superscript to see content of the footnote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;footnote-5&#34;&gt;Footnote-5&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;You can create footnotes like this[^footnote].
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[^footnote]: Here is the &lt;span style=&#34;font-style:italic&#34;&gt;*text*&lt;/span&gt; of the &lt;span style=&#34;font-weight:bold&#34;&gt;**footnote**&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will produce dddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddd:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create footnotes like this&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:6&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mouse on the ‘footnote’ superscript to see content of the footnote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;example footnote show.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;strong&gt;footnote-1&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:3&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;strong&gt;footnote-2&lt;/strong&gt;. Here is the text of the footnote-2. Here is the text of the footnote-2. Here is the text of the footnote-2. Here is the text of the footnote-2.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;The world’s fastest framework for building websites | Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:3&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:4&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;strong&gt;footnote-3&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:4&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:5&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;strong&gt;footnote-4&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:5&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:6&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; of the &lt;strong&gt;footnote-5&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:6&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials: Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/3-syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>itspedia@itspedia.com (itspedia)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/knowledge/3-syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;More detail: &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/syntax-highlighting/&#34;&gt;Syntax Highlighting | Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-js&#34; data-lang=&#34;js&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;helloWorld&lt;/span&gt; () {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;alert&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-java&#34; data-lang=&#34;java&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;public&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;HelloWorld&lt;/span&gt; {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;public&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;(String&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;[]&lt;/span&gt; args) {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    System.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;out&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;println&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;);
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  }
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-kotlin&#34; data-lang=&#34;kotlin&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;package&lt;/span&gt; hello
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;fun&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;(args: Array&amp;lt;String&amp;gt;) {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  println(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-c&#34; data-lang=&#34;c&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;#include&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;stdio.h&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;/* Hello */&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;int&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;void&lt;/span&gt;){
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;printf&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;);
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-cpp&#34; data-lang=&#34;cpp&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// &amp;#39;Hello World!&amp;#39; program
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;#include&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;int&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;(){
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  std&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;cout &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; std&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;endl;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-cs&#34; data-lang=&#34;cs&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;using&lt;/span&gt; System;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;HelloWorld&lt;/span&gt;{
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;public&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;static&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;void&lt;/span&gt; Main(){
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    System.Console.WriteLine(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;);
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  }
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  Hello, World!
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;body&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;lt;/&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;html&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-go&#34; data-lang=&#34;go&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;package&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;fmt&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;func&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;()
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;{
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;   &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;fmt&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Printf&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!\n&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;);
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-scala&#34; data-lang=&#34;scala&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;object&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;HelloWorld&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;with&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Application&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Console&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;println&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-php&#34; data-lang=&#34;php&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;php&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;echo&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;Hello, World!&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;?&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#960050;background-color:#1e0010&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;print(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-named-code-block&#34;&gt;no named code block&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;## this is a comment
$ echo this is a command
this is a command

## edit the file
$vi foo.md
+++
date = &amp;#34;2014-09-28&amp;#34;
title = &amp;#34;creating a new theme&amp;#34;
+++

bah and humbug
:wq

## show it
$ cat foo.md
+++
date = &amp;#34;2014-09-28&amp;#34;
title = &amp;#34;creating a new theme&amp;#34;
+++

bah and humbug
$&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlight-shortcode&#34;&gt;highlight shortcode&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;

  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;

  
  &lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shortcode&#34; data-lang=&#34;shortcode&#34;&gt;{{&amp;lt; highlight go &amp;#34;linenos=table,hl_lines=8 15-17,linenostart=199&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}}
// ... code
{{&amp;lt; /highlight &amp;gt;}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;result:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight-container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;button class=&#34;copy-code-btn outline&#34;&gt;Copy&lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;display:grid;&#34;&gt;
&lt;table style=&#34;border-spacing:0;padding:0;margin:0;border:0;&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td style=&#34;vertical-align:top;padding:0;margin:0;border:0;&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;display:grid;&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;199
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;200
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;201
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;202
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;203
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;204
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;205
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;206
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;207
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;208
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;209
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;210
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;211
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;212
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;213
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;214
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;215
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;216
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;217
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;218
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;219
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;white-space:pre;-webkit-user-select:none;user-select:none;margin-right:0.4em;padding:0 0.4em 0 0.4em;color:#7f7f7f&#34;&gt;220
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;vertical-align:top;padding:0;margin:0;border:0;;width:100%&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;display:grid;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-go&#34; data-lang=&#34;go&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// GetTitleFunc returns a func that can be used to transform a string to&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// title case.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// The supported styles are&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// - &amp;#34;Go&amp;#34; (strings.Title)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// - &amp;#34;AP&amp;#34; (see https://www.apstylebook.com/)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex; background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// - &amp;#34;Chicago&amp;#34; (see http://www.chicagomanualofstyle.org/home.html)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;//&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#75715e&#34;&gt;// If an unknown or empty style is provided, AP style is what you get.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;func&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;GetTitleFunc&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;style&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;string&lt;/span&gt;) &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;func&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;s&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;string&lt;/span&gt;) &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;string&lt;/span&gt; {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;switch&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;strings&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;ToLower&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;style&lt;/span&gt;) {
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;case&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;go&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;:
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;strings&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Title&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex; background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;case&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#e6db74&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;chicago&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;:
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex; background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;tc&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;:=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;transform&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;NewTitleConverter&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;transform&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;ChicagoStyle&lt;/span&gt;)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex; background-color:#3c3d38&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;tc&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Title&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;default&lt;/span&gt;:
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;tc&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;:=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;transform&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;NewTitleConverter&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;transform&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;APStyle&lt;/span&gt;)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;    &lt;span style=&#34;color:#66d9ef&#34;&gt;return&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;tc&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;color:#a6e22e&#34;&gt;Title&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  }
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
